

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

UTAD

2022 - PRESENT

SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY COURSE

Secundária de Fafe 2019 - 2022

INTERESTS

Programming

Technology

Design

Phone

+351 967138113

Email

lemosluis547@gmail.com

Website

https://luisandrelemos.github.io/

Address

Fafe, 4820-707

LUÍS LEMOS

SOFTWARE ENGINEER STUDENT

ABOUT ME

Hi, my name is Luís Lemos and I am a Sofware Engineer student, athlete and technology enthusiast. I have experience in software development and programming in several languages, as well as skills in project management, problem solving and teamwork. Additionally, I am a dedicated athlete and committed to maintaining a healthy and active lifestyle. I believe that my combination of technical skills and personal dedication can contribute to exciting and innovative projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020-PRESENT SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR IN RESIDENTIAL AND COMMERCIAL NETWORKS

Nuno Elétrico LDA

I work weekends where I am responsible for installing and programming home automation, surveillance cameras, video intercoms, routers and switches. This experience allows me to develop technical skills in the area of technology and security, as well as improve my communication and customer service skills.

2020 - 2021 MEDICAL CLINIC REBRANDING

Consultório Dr Ernani

Rebranding of a Private Medical Clinic

SKILLS

Customer Service

C/C++/C#/PHP

Haskell

Python/NodeJS

GIT/Bootstrap